I know!
Monday, July 20th
Hilarious, right?
Hey, Asamura. Head in the clouds?
Heat getting to you?
No, I'm fine.
Anyway, I hear you and Narasaka
have been getting awfully close lately.
Huh?
Haven't you?
I just asked her some questions about studying.
I hear she goes around
calling you "Big Brother."
Oh... Yeah, that...
Well, anyway,
if you're having a romantic awakening,
you can ask me for advice.
As a relationship expert, I'll do everything
I can to back my buddy up in his love life.
When that time really does come,
I'll be counting on you.
Episode 6 "Sweet 'n' Sour Pork and Rain"
Hey, it's Asamura-kun!
What's up? Fancy running into you
on the way out of here, huh?
Narasaka-san...
Oh, you two are together today?
Let's go home together!
Huh? But... why?
Huh? What do you mean, "why"?
This is the perfect chance!
For what? I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I mean, we're all headed to Saki's place!
Huh?
Sorry. I asked her to help me study at home.
Oh, so that's why.
But isn't this awkward for Narasaka-san,
with us walking home together?
Not at all! I don't have anything against it!
I mean, you're going to the same place.
Why would you walk home separately?
Right, Saki?
Well, you have a point.
Yeah...
Well, I guess we're stuck with it this time.
Maybe Maaya was the wrong person to ask...
I'm home!
Uh, this is actually my house.
First one in!
Sorry for all the noise today.
Hello there, Sofa-kun!
You're nice and squishy today!
It won't bother me. Good luck studying.
I'm happy to see you, too!
Thanks.
Wanna do it here?
Let's go over there.
Oh, I'll get us something to drink.
Thanks!
Hmm, let's see...
Hold on a sec.
Okay.
So, here...
Oh, sorry. I'll get started on dinner.
Oh, that's okay. I wasn't trying to pressure you.
I'll take care of it.
Huh?
I have the day off from work.
You should concentrate on your studies.
Thanks. That's a huge help.
Hmm, yes, very nice.
You're giving off good husband vibes,
Asamura-kun.
Maybe I should start with the rice?
Asamura-kun!
If you want a drink, the fridge is—
That's not what I'm here for!
I came to see how you were doing.
Having a little trouble, maybe?
Actually, this is a little
embarrassing for me.
I thought I could figure it
out if I had a recipe,
but I can't make any sense of it.
I see, I see.
Hey, Saki! You're good to spend the
rest of the time just reviewing, right?
Yeah. Thanks for the help.
Okay, then, give it your best shot!
I'm gonna help Asamura-kun cook.
Huh? Er, okay... but that's asking a lot of you—
It's fine, it's fine!
I'll stun you with a taste
of my housewifey powers!
Mwa-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Okay. Thanks.
All right, then!
I'm happy to offer my guidance and support
to Big Brother here, our new cook!
Let's do this!
Y-Yeah, let's do it.
Did you draw it?
Let's go!
Okay!
Over here!
Ken, ken, pa!
Recipes for Students Studying for Entrance Exams
Perfect if you need to count on your body! Handpicked recipes
Sweet 'n' Sour Pork
How to Make
So, Asamura-kun, are you sure
there's nothing between you and Saki?
It would be trouble if there was.
But you're basically strangers, right?
You aren't even related by blood.
Why are you so curious about
my relationship with Ayase-san?
Why? I'm not really sure.
I just get this feeling that
Saki's changed a little.
Huh.
Like, for example, she's using
more perfume than before.
Did you notice?
Not at all.
Thank goodness! It would've
been so creepy if you had.
Quit setting traps.
And last year, she only used wet wipes
when she got sweaty instead of perfume.
Those seem to be all she really needs,
though, so it's not like it's a problem.
But she's using more this year?
Yes! And that's the behavior of a person
who's conscious of a special someone!
That's what Detective Maaya-chan's
intuition is telling her, Watson-kun!
Huh.
What a weak reaction!
Jeez. I'm telling you a super cute girl
has probably got you on her mind,
and you don't care at all?
That's one way to put it, but I think it's
only natural for her to be thinking about me.
I knew it! So the feeling's mutual!
That's not it.
When you live with someone
of the opposite sex,
of course you're going to be
more mindful of the way you smell.
Huh? Is that all there is to it?
But look! She's even watching you right now!
She probably realized that
we were talking about her.
Your voice is pretty loud, Narasaka-san.
Aww. I'm convinced it's one
of those love things, though.
If you keep hounding your friend about that,
she's going to get really annoyed.
Too late! Saki's already
really annoyed with me!
Oh! Nice timing!
And that's it for Maaya's Cooking Hour today!
This is delicious.
I'm really glad you like it.
I mean, sweet 'n' sour pork?
You really went out of your way for me.
You might be right.
Thanks. I really do appreciate it.
Sure. So how's the studying going?
Thanks to your help, I was easily able to
answer the questions Maaya came up with.
Oh, good.
But then she got mad because she thinks
my study method is roundabout and inefficient.
Yeah, honestly, it might not be
the most direct way, after all.
You don't need to worry.
It's working for me.
I'm sure I'll do fine on the test tomorrow, too.
Yeah?
I'm rooting for you, Ayase-san.
Thank you, Asamura-kun.
Delicious.
Just delicious.
Thank you.
Tuesday, July 21st
What's up? Something bugging you today?
Huh?
Oh, no. I'm good.
Yeah? Well, see you tomorrow.
Sure.
Are you all right?
I've never seen my sweet junior
so off his game before.
I'm really sorry.
I'm going to head home.
I'm home.
Heavy rain showers hit central Tokyo.
With the rising temperatures and humidity,
the rain may be accompanied
by lightning in some areas.
The storm may also affect public transit.
Heavy precipitation is expected
to continue late into the evening.
This is the current situation
here in Shibuya, Tokyo.
Large raindrops are pounding
down upon the pavement.
Some station platforms and retail
facilities are experiencing flooding,
resulting in widespread chaos.
It's rush hour right now, and the trains
are absolutely packed with passengers.
Tutor me in modern lit.
Thank you. You're a really good teacher.
I'll try listening to it tonight.
Stations are restricting access to platforms,
You okay in the rain?
which are likely to remain
crowded for the time being.
You okay in the rain?
This concludes our live report from Shibuya.
Thank you very much.
Next up is a special sports report.
If you end up getting home late
Where are you right now?
I know it's late, but can I ask you something?
How did it go?
It went fine
Thanks
That helped
Where are you right now?
I'll trust in you and do my best, Asamura-kun.
Huh? Oh, I'm sorry! You okay?
Asamura-kun? Are you going somewhere?
Uh... No, I just...
You were late, and it was raining so hard.
I couldn't get a hold of you, so I just...
I was worried maybe the test didn't go great
and you were off... crying somewhere.
You must have really been worried.
I'm genuinely sorry about that.
But as for the test...
Well, to be honest,
I didn't exactly get the best result.
Q2
Q3
Q4
Q5
Modern Lit
First Term Exam
Retake
But that's a passing score...
Asamura-kun, you got 96 points, right?
I didn't beat you.
It's so frustrating.
Don't scare me like that.
Sorry to make you worry.
I also went somewhere different for groceries.
Did you go all the way to the department store?
Did you want to celebrate passing
the test with something special?
That's half right and half not.
Can I get a practice answer?
I wanted to show my gratitude.
I know that might sound
kind of condescending,
but I really mean it.
I haven't done anything to earn your gratitude.
We made a fair exchange.
No. You did so much for me
leading up to the test.
You introduced me to new music,
taught me how to read modern literature...
That isn't exactly a whole lot.
And yesterday, you even made me dinner.
Compared to all the cooking
you've done for over a month,
I don't think one dinner comes close.
Like I said, I like to give more than I take.
So today, I'm going to make you
the most elegant meal I can.
Or do you feel like you can only
lean on someone older than you?
Huh?
You mean Yomiuri-senpai?
What's she got to do with this?
As far as I know, she's the one and only
person you really trust to have your back.
Well, that's just because
we work together so much.
You can depend on me, too.
Just like you depend on her at work.
I want you to depend on me for stuff at home.
Or we can just say your little sister is really
stubborn. Will you go along with it then?
Speaking as your big brother,
if I let you treat me today,
would you consider that mission success?
Yes. That would make me happy.
How long are we going
to stay in here, anyway?
You're right. Let's get home.
Yeah.
By the way, can I ask you one more thing?
What?
I messaged you...
Oh, about that...
I keep running down my phone battery
listening to that music you sent me.
Asamura
Ayase
Ah, that explains it.
Wednesday, July 22nd
So, uh, summer vacation starts tomorrow.
Don't go too crazy.
And, well...
Yeah. See you!
Goodbye!
I'm off.
Oh, you're sure in a rush.
I gotta get to work.
Looks like you're over
whatever was bothering you.
Yeah, I guess so.
Later.
Yeah.
Work hard, young man!
Huh?
Asamura-kun.
If you're tired, don't push yourself.
Take a little break.
Boss, who was that just now?
Oh, she's here for a job interview.
What's her name?
Huh?
Oh, her name is Ayase Saki.
Episode 7 "Feelings and Summer Vacation"